ccu.edu 2018-08-16

# Online Privacy Policy | Colorado Christian University

## Protecting Your Privacy on CCU's Website

At Colorado Christian University, we are committed to protecting your privacy as a visitor to our website.

### Scope of the Privacy Policy

This policy applies to website visitors, current and prospective students, alumni, donors, and any other user of services offered through a Colorado Christian University website.

### Security of your Personal Information

When you visit the CCU website, you may voluntarily choose to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone numbers, credit card or bank account numbers. Your use of the online services available on our website amounts to your consent to the collection and use of the personal information provided.

CCU will not sell, disseminate, disclose, trade, transfer, share, lease or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party without your consent, unless it is necessary to provide a service that you requested (e.g., processing a credit card or electronic funds transaction, or sending you information), or to comply with applicable laws and regulations.

### How Information is Collected

A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on a visitor's hard drive while they are visiting the Colorado Christian University website. We may utilize a short-lived form of cookie when you visit this site. At CCU, a cookie is only used to identify one unique visitor to our website from another visitor during a particular session. A session is the period of active site-use while that unique visitor is linked to our server. We may use cookie technology during a session as a tool to carry forward your input information during a visit to the University’s website. This enables the visitor to input information once and have that information appear later when filling out a form on our website. Examples include, but are not limited to, forms related to the admission and enrollment process, as well as online giving and bill payment. No personally identifiable information is stored on the cookie.

### Text Messaging

By texting CCU or FAITH to 777555 or FUTURE to 69979, you consent to receive mobile promotional text messages from Colorado Christian University and/or The Centennial Institute at the phone number you provided. Your consent to receive text messages (opt-in) is not required for admission to Colorado Christian University or to buy goods/svcs from The Centennial Institute. If you wish to opt out of receiving text messages, or if you have errantly received a marketing text message without opting in to the program, you can cancel the program at any time by texting STOP CCU, STOP FAITH to 777555 or STOP FUTURE to 69979. Opting out of receiving text messages will only affect your receipt of text messages. You may still receive messages from Colorado Christian University via email or other methods.

You may text HELP CCU or HELP FAITH to 777555 to receive additional information regarding Colorado Christian University’s Mobile Alerts Program. Standard message and data rates may apply. While Colorado Christian University does not charge any fee for using its service, your use of the service via text, multimedia, or instant message on your mobile phone or any other device is subject to the standard message and data charges per your carrier's rate plan.

### Exceptions to this Policy

While Colorado Christian University uses security measures to protect against the unauthorized access to the personal information of a visitor to our website, we cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication transmitted to or from our website or email through the Internet. In addition, any non-CCU websites accessed via hyperlinks from a CCU website are not controlled by the University, and are not subject to this privacy policy.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without providing you with advance notice of our intent to make the changes.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us via mail or phone listed on our site on our Contact Us page.
